Even in the midst of flowing time, oppression spins round and round.
I can't even see the heart that's leaving me, didn't you know?
I can't even get myself to move, slipping through the cracks of time.
I don't know anything about what's around me,
I'm just me and no more.
Am I dreaming? Or seeing nothing?
Are my words useless even if I speak?
I'm just tired of being sad
I should go on without feeling anything
Even if you give me the words; I'm at
a loss for
My heart just won't pay attention
If I can move, if everything changes, it will go dark.
Is there a future for someone like me?
Will I still exist in a world like this?
Is this painful? Is it sad?
Not even knowing myself.
I'm just tired even of walking, I don't even understand people.
If someone like me can change, if I change, will it turn white?
Even in the midst of flowing time, oppression spins round and round.
I can't even see the heart that's leaving me, didn't you know?
I can't even get myself to move slipping through the cracks of time.
I don't know anything about what's around me, I'm just me and no more.
Am I dreaming? Or seeing nothing? Are my words useless even if I speak?
I'm just tired of being sad;
I should go on without feeling anything.
Even if you give me the words; I'm at
a loss for
My heart just won't pay attention.
If I can move, if everything changes, it will go dark.
Is there a future to come out of this useless
time?
Will I exist in a place like this?
If I wanted to tell you what kind of person I
am, the words I'd use would be "good for nothing".
Will I exist in a place like this?
Will
I exist in a time like this?
If someone like me can change, if I change, will it turn white?
Am I dreaming now? Or seeing nothing?
Are my words useless even if I speak?
I'm just tired of being sad;
I should go on without feeling anything.
Even if you give me the words I'm at a
loss for, my heart just won't pay attention.
If I can move, if everything changes, it will all go dark.
If I move, If I move,
everything will break, everything will break.
If I'm sad, if I'm sad, will my heart be able to turn white?
I still know nothing about you, about me, about anything.
If I can open my heavy eyelids, if I break everything, turn black!